Chris and his dad have accidentally changed bodies - but no big deal. Chris gets
the Jag and the Gold Card. Dad gets the fake ID and the bio final.
Like Father Like Son is a comedy, fantasy film directed by Rod Daniel.
Jack Hammond has best chances to become medical superintendent in the clinic.
So he's completely absorbed in his work and has no understanding
for his teenage son Chris' problems with school.
By accident one of them drinks a brain-exchanging
serum, and it switches their identities.
This leads of course to extraordinary complications in school and at work, but
also to insight in the problems and feelings of each other.
Dr. Jack Hammond / Chris Hammond, played by Dudley Moore.
Chris Hammond / Dr. Jack Hammond, played by Kirk Cameron.
Ginnie Armbruster, played by Margaret Colin.
Dr. Amy Larkin, played by Catherine Hicks.
Dr. Larry Armbruster, played by Patrick O'Neal.
Clarence / Trigger, played by Sean Astin.
Like Father Like Son is a 1987 American fantasy comedy film directed by Rod Daniel and starring
Dudley Moore and Kirk Cameron about a father and son who magically switch bodies.
The film was released by Tri-Star Pictures on October 2, 1987, and received mostly negative
reviews from critics while grossing $34.4 million against a $10.5 million budget.
The film explores themes of high school, role reversal,
remake, doctor, high school friends.
The tone is lighthearted.